[
    {
        "Question": "How does idev work?",
        "Answer Given": "The idev command submits a batch job",
        "Score": 0.06679823994636536,
        "Actual Answer": "submits a batch job that creates a copy of the batch environment"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does idev do?",
        "Answer Given": "creates an interactive development environment from the user's login window",
        "Score": 0.08500891923904419,
        "Actual Answer": "creates and interactive development environment from the user's login window"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the terminal command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "SSH",
        "Score": 0.3887535631656647,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "SSH",
        "Score": 0.4205184876918793,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much time will the system report the job status?",
        "Answer Given": "every 4 seconds",
        "Score": 0.9484819769859314,
        "Actual Answer": "every 4 seconds"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens on the first time launching idev?",
        "Answer Given": "idev will prompt you for the project name",
        "Score": 0.12600040435791016,
        "Actual Answer": "idev will prompt you for the project name and then save your selection as the default interactive account"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you start an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "Stampede3 Skylake development node",
        "Score": 0.03723021224141121,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do launch an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "ibrun myapp",
        "Score": 0.2559795677661896,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command launces an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "SSH",
        "Score": 0.39156195521354675,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does -m do with idev",
        "Answer Given": "minutes            sets time in minutes",
        "Score": 0.21575011312961578,
        "Actual Answer": "sets time in minutes"
    }
]